<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="comedy.xsl" type="text/xsl" ?>
<catalog>
            <genre id="Comedy">
            <!--facts for tab 1-->
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>51% Of People Think Stormy Weather Affects Cloud Computing.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Marge Simpson</name>
                    <fact>You can change your language on Facebook to "Pirate."</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Bart Simpson</name>
                    <fact>1 in 10 Americans thinks HTML --the language of web pages-- is a sexually transmitted disease.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Lisa Simpson</name>
                    <fact>In the U.S., there's an official Rock Paper Scissors League</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Maggie Simpson</name>
                    <fact>The American secret service tried to spike Hitler's food with female hormones to feminize him.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>User</name>
                    <fact>Submitted Fact</fact>
                </facts>
            <facts><name>RSS</name><fact>There is a new fact over on Random Facts!!!</fact></facts></genre>
            <genre id="Sport">
            <!--facts for tab 2-->
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>In 1969, El Salvador waged war on Honduras after it lost against it in a soccer match.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>FIFA has more member countries than the U.N.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>The city of Lusail, host of the 2022 FIFA World Cup Final game, does not exist yet.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>In 1967, the Nigerian Civil War ground to a halt for two days because both sides wanted to watch soccer player Pele in an exhibition match.</fact>
                    
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>Argentina's retired soccer player Diego Maradona has his own religion made by his fans.</fact>
                </facts>
            </genre>
            <genre id="History">
            <!--facts for tab 3-->
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>The eruption of Krakatoa in 1883 was the loudest sound in recorded history, heard 3,000 miles (4800 KM) away.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>Hitler led the first public anti-smoking campaign in modern history.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>From 1814 to 1830, the flag of the Kingdom of France was plain white.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>Life expectancy in Ancient Rome was from 20 to 30 years.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>Christmas was illegal in the U.S. until 1836 as it was considered an Ancient Pagan Holiday.</fact>
                </facts>
            </genre>
            <genre id="Random">
            <!--facts for tab 4-->
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>The iconic windows 95 startup sound was composed on a mac.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>The first webcam was created in Cambridge to check the status of a coffee pot.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>50% of Internet users will quit waiting for a video to load after 10 seconds.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>Earth is the only place in the Solar System where water can be present in its three states: solid, liquid and vapour.</fact>
                </facts>
                <facts>
                    <name>Homer Simpson</name>
                    <fact>The Earth lost 40% of its wildlife in the past 40 years, according to the WWF.</fact>
                </facts>
            </genre>
    </catalog>
